Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5305
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arnesto Paint Company vs. Local N-12129, OCAWIU, 11/14/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 11)
  Decision - Discharge, Damages, Leaving Plant Without Permission, Vacation
- 1895 Morris Avenue vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 11/14/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 12)
  Decision - Crew size
- Contractors Production Corp. vs. Local 1205, IBT, 11/15/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 13)
  Decision - Cost of Living Increase
- Van Dorn Realty Corporation vs. Local 670, Stationary Engineers, 11/18/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 14)
- Donnelly-Blantharn and Co., Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 12/16/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 15)
- Skalet Jewelry Manufacturing Co., vs. Local 1, IJWU, 12/17/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 16)
  Decision - Recall
- Regina Stern vs. Local 1, BSEIU, 12/19/57 (Box 5.1, Folder 17)
- 2095 Holding Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 12/18/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 18)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Welfare Fund.
- Acme Gauge and Instrument Company vs. Local 222, IJWU, 12/18/57, 1957 (Box 5.1, Folder 19)
- 266 Riverside Avenue vs. Local 1, BSEIU, 1/7/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 20)
  Decision - Penalties
- Norton's Department Store vs. District 65, RWDSU, 1/8/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 21)
  Decision - Seniority, Layoff, Pension Fund
- Continental Silver Company, Inc. vs. Local 485, IUE, 1/9/58 (Box 5.1, Folder 22)
- Burner Service Corporation vs. Local 463, IUE, 1/14/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 23)
- Eton Silver Company vs. Local 485, IUE, 1/15/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 24)
  Decision - Lay-off
- White Turkey Restaurants vs. Local 11, CSRL & SF, 1/24/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 25)
  Decision - Discharge, Rules
- Aron Rojak vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 1/29/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 26)
  Decision - Discharge, Alcoholism
- Brooklyn Hand Laundrymen's Association vs. Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board, 2/19/58 (Box 5.1, Folder 27)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Overtime, Workweek, Holiday Pay
- Photo Crafts, Inc. vs. Local 24910, Blueprint, Photostat and Photo Employees Union, 3/4/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 28)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Holidays, Vacations
- Linen Supply Institute vs. Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board, 3/4/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 29)
  Decision - Overtime, Lunch Periods
- Dugan Brothers, Inc. vs. Local 802, IBT, 3/5/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 30)
  Decision - Discharge, Carelessness and Negligence
- 4516 Park Avenue vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 3/7/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 31)
  Decision - Discharge, Dual Employment
- Kaufman Stores vs. District 65, RWDSU, 3/7/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 32)
- Norman Salit vs. Local 377, RWDSU, 3/7/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 33)
  Decision - Wages, Vacation
- Royal Novelty Company, Inc. vs. Local 169, ACWA, 3/11/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 34)
- Sylvia Gray Hand Laundry and Cleaners vs. Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board, 3/14/58 (ACWA), 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 35)
- Regal Laundry vs. Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board (ACWA), 3/17/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 36)
- General Bronze Corporation vs. Local 66, Architectural and Engineering Guild, 3/18/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 37)
- Brooklyn Hand Laundrymen's Association vs. Laundry Workers Joint Board of Greater NY, 4/1/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 38)
- Lifton, Gold and Asher vs. District 65, RWDSU, 4/2/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 39)
- C & S Marks, Inc. vs. Local 305, RWDSU, 4/2/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 40)
  Decision - Discharge, Rates of Pay, Severance Pay, Overtime Pay
- Ludwig Dreyfus vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 4/2/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 41)
- John Reber Baking Corporation vs. Local 802, IBT, 4/10/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 42)
  Decision - Discipline, Improper Personal Conduct
- Ernest DeMaria vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 4/16/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 43)
  Decision - Discharge, Financial Irresponsibility
- C. Ludwig Baumann Company, Inc. vs. Local 1115E, RCIA, 4/21/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 44)
  Decision - Bonus, Fringe Benefits
- Effanjay Pen Company vs. Local 1115A, Warehouse, Production and Sales Employees, 4/23/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 45)
- 262 E. 2nd Street Corporation vs. Local 377, United Service Employees, 4/23/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 46)
- Simon Zucker Company vs. Local 169, ACWA, 4/30/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 47)
- Moulding Corporation of America vs. Local 223, Toy Novelty Workers of America, 5/1/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 48)
  Decision - Discharge, Seniority, Rates of Pay, Holiday Pay
- Irwin Properties Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 5/12/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 49)
- 245 Corporation vs. Local 2, IUBSE, 5/13/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 50)
- Stanley Equipment Corporation vs. Local 150, United Mechanics Union, 5/16/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 51)
- Epicure Diner Inc. vs. Local 1115, Restaurant, Dining Room and Luncheonette Employees Union, 5/20/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 52)
  Decision - Discharge, Layoff
- Liberty Music Shops, Inc. vs. Local 854, IBT, 5/23/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 53)
- Mechanical Steel Tubing Corporation vs. Local 365, UAW, 5/27/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 54)
- Bent Glass Works, Inc. vs. Local 13543, District 50, UMW, 6/10/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 55)
- Permalum Window Manufacturing Corporation vs. Local 136A, UAW, 6/10/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 56)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Fringe Benefits
- East Meadow Sanitation Service vs. Local 813, IBT, 6/24/58, 1958 (Box 5.1, Folder 57)
- Hanlon & Goodman Industries, Inc. vs. Local 303, Bushmaker's Union, 10/25/67. #67-310, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Decision - Overtime, Insubordination
- Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority vs. District Council 37 and Local 1396, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1/68. #67-312, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Finding of Facts and Recommendations, Fact-Finder's Notes, BNA Labor Relations, Relations Reports (decisions of past cases), Employer and Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, General Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- Styl-Rite Optics, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 1/2/68. #67-313, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Decision - Assignment to Work Outside Classification, Work Stoppage, Insubordination
- Pan American World Airways vs. Local 504, TWU, 12/8/67. #67-314, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Decision - Falsification
- Rowe Manufacturing Co. vs. Local 950, UAW, 1/16/68. #67-316, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Decision - Classification of Jobs, Transfers, Bumping
- New York City Housing Authority vs. Local 237, City Employees Union (CEU), 1/68. #67-318, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Al Schacht and Jakger Restaurant Assn., Inc. vs. Local 15, Bartenders Union of NYC, 12/19/67. #67-319 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Decision - Contracting out, Vacation pay
- American Machine & Foundry Co. vs. IAMAW, 2/28/68. #67-310, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Decision - Job Classifications
- Interstate Container Corp. vs. Local 300, IBPSPMW, 12/13/67. #67-322, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Decision - Intoxicating Liquor in Work Area
- Simmons Co. vs. Local 420, UIU, 1/16/68. #67-331., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Decision, General Correspondence - Holiday
- Williams Press, Inc. vs. Local 23, Albany, Printing Pressmen, Assistants Union (APPAOU), 12/15/67. #67-332, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Hearing Transcripts, Union Exhibits, Company Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes on Case, Correspondence - Rates of Pay, Wages
- J.F.D. Manufacturing Company vs. Local 854, IBT, 7/1/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 1)
- Brill Estates Company vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 7/2/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 2)
- Kendon Holding Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 7/2/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 3)
- Stella D'Oro Biscuit Company, Inc. vs. Local 550, IBT, 7/2/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 4)
- Lincoln Meat Packers Corporation, vs. Local 640, Butcher Workmen's Union, 7/14/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 5)
  Decision - Discharge, Tardiness, Improper Job Attitude
- J.F.D. Manufacturing Company vs. Local 854, IBT, 7/15/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 6)
- Donnapower Realty Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 7/15/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 7)
- Estate of Isidore Jaffee, d/b/a Jaffe's Army & Navy Store vs. Harlem Labor Union, 7/16/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 8)
  Decision - Discharge, Improper Work Practices
- Petroleum Heat and Power Co., Inc. vs. Local 638, Metal Trades Branch, 7/22/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 9)
- Schlossman's Inc. vs. Local 635, RCIA, 8/5/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 10)
  Decision - Discharge, Tardiness, Improper Work Practices
- King Kullen Grocery vs. Local 1500, Retail Food Clerks Union, 8/7/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 11)
- Astor Furniture Company, Inc. vs. Local 853, N.Y. Furniture and Merchants Association, 8/11/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 12)
- Westchester Hills Country Club vs. Local 178, HREIU, 8/15/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 13)
- Anchor Wire Corporation vs. Local 463, IUE, 8/18/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 14)
  Decision - Call-in
- Beechwood Homes Inc. vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 8/21/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 15)
- Pechter Baking Company, Inc. vs. Local 3, ABCWU, 8/25/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 16)
- Koeppel Metal Furniture Co. vs. Local 810, IBT, 8/27/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 17)
- Manhattan Wire Goods Company vs. Local 810, IBT, 9/8/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 18)
- Our Own Food Products vs. Local 422, IJWU, 9/8/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 19)
  Decision - Fights and Altercations
- Swift and Company vs. Local 277, IBT, 9/9/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 20)
- Simco Products vs. Local 258, Warehousemen and Processing Employees Union, 10/7/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 21)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Working Conditions
- Earl Scheib, Inc. vs. Local 284, Association of Production, Maintenance and Distributing Workers of America, 10/16/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 22)
- Aaron Bring Chevrolet Company, Inc. vs. Local 259, UAW, 10/20/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 23)
- Avis, Inc. vs. Local 643, IBT, 11/3/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 24)
  Decision - Discharge, Theft, Improper Work Practices
- Eden Plastics Corporation vs. Local 422, IJWU, 11/3/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 25)
  Decision - Lay-off, Seniority
- Karlan and Bleicher, Inc. vs. Local 1, IJWU, 11/5/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 26)
- Tally-Ho Trading Company vs. District 54, RWDSU, 11/10/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 27)
  Decision - Lay-off, Pension Fund
- Dis-Play-Well, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 11/10/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 28)
- Earl Scheib of East Bronx, Inc. vs. Local 284, Association of Processing, Maintenance and Distributing Workers of America, 11/12/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 29)
- Argon Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 12/2/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 30)
- Rushmore Steel Corporation vs. Local 810, IBT, 12/4/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 31)
  Decision - Classification of Jobs, Interpretation of Contract
- Volner Manufacturing Company vs. Local 10, IBPNOE, 12/4/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 32)
  Decision - Discharge, Improper Personal Conduct, Plant Rules
- P.G. Whitman, Inc. vs. Local 815, IBT, 12/10/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 33)
- Falcon Buick, Inc. vs. Local 259, UAW, 12/22/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 34)
  Decision - Assignment of Jobs, Elimination of Jobs
- Bakherb Realty Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 12/23/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 35)
  Decision - Discharge, Incompetence & Inefficiency
- Cortile Restaurant, Inc. vs. Local 1, Dining Room Employees, 12/23/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 36)
- Frank E. Kipp vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 12/31/58, 1958 (Box 6.1, Folder 37)
- Metaplast Process Co. vs. Local 476, United Brotherhood of Industrial Workers, 1/13/59., 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 38)
- Krug Baking Company vs. Local 50, ABCWU, 1/13/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 39)
- Colonial Sand and Stone Inc. vs. Local 282, IBT, 1/14/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 40)
- Acey Auto Corporation vs. Local 259, UAW, 1/15/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 41)
  Decision - Standards of Production, Rates of Pay
- Michaels and Co., Inc. vs. Local 138, IBT, 1/20/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 42)
- Electrical Insulation Co., Inc. vs. Local 431, IUE, 1/21/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 43)
- Walter Balfour and Co., Inc. vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 2/2/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 44)
  Decision - Discharge, Overtime, Contract Silence
- Sherwin-Williams Co., vs. Local 1310, paint, Varnish and Allied Products, 2/6/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 45)
- Timslog Realty Corporation and D&G Realty, Inc. vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 2/19/59 (Box 6.1, Folder 46)
- S.B. Thomas, Inc. vs. Local 802, IBT, 2/20/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 47)
  Decision - Discharge, Plant Rules
- Oneko Manufacturing Company, Inc. vs. TWUA, NY Jt. Bd. 2/26/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 48)
- Clifford Davidson Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 2/26/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 49)
- Lomart Industries, vs. Local 422 Industrial Workers Union, 2/27/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 50)
- Optical Products Corp. vs. Local 408, UOWU, 3/26/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 51)
- Vogerd, Inc. vs. Local 90, Organized Workers Union, 3/26/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 52)
  Decision - Discharge, Overtime, Vacation Pay, Negligence and Carelessness
- Plastic Art Metalizing Corporation vs. Local 854, IBT, 4/7/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 53)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Holidays, Vacation, Welfare Fund
- Stage Delicatessen, Inc. vs. Local 1, Restaurant and Hotel Employees Union, 4/7/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 54)
- Jacob Siegel and Eva Cohen vs. Local 377, United Service Employees, 4/14/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 55)
- Tel-Rad Electronics Corporation vs. Local 225, IJWU, 4/14/59, 1959 (Box 6.1, Folder 56)
- J. Cintolo d/b/a Joseph's Beauty Salon vs. Local 150A, BCU, 1/30/68. #67-334, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Mailings, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 3/22/68. #67-335, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Decision - Successor Company
- Union Labor Life Insurance Co. vs. Local 153, Office & Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), 2/68. #67-336, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Decision - Job Descriptions, Testing of Employees
- U.S. Army Watervliet Arsenal vs. Lodge 2352, American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE), 12/28/67. #67-337, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Background Facts, Employer Briefs, Employee Briefs, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence. Issue - Promotion
- A. Goodman & Sons, Inc. vs. Local 269, BCW, 2/6/68. #68-338, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Decision - Demotion
- Farmlea Dairy Inc. vs. Local 338, IBT, 2/6/68. #68-339, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Decision - Consolidation & Merger, Bumping
- Toms River Board of Education vs. Toms River Teachers Association, 2/2/68. #68-340, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Recommendations for settlement, arbitrator's bill. Issue - Contract modification
- Brook-Hattan Transportation Inc. vs. Local 355, Amalgamated Union, 3/4/68. #68-341, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Roval El Patio, Inc. vs. Local 164, Hotel and Restaurant Employees (HRE), 3/28/68. #68-343, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Newark Board of Education vs. Newark Teachers Association, 3/28/68. #68-344, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Proposal of Mediator - Contract Modification
- Mary Palomo, d/b/a Silhouette Beauty Shop vs. Local 150A, BCU, 3/14/68. #68-346, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Breyer Ice Cream, Div. of National Dairy Products Corp. vs. Local 757, IBT, 3/29/68. #68-347, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Decision - Seniority, Bidding for Foremen's Job
- S.M. Rose Corp. vs. Local 259, UAW, 4/8/68, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Decision - Plant Rules
- Electrical Industries, Div. of Phillips Electronics & Pharmaceutical, Ind. Vs. Local 102, IBT, 4/25/68. #68-350, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Rhodia Inc. vs. Local 8-622, OCAWIU, 5/20/68. #68-351, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Decision - Contract Modification
- Facile Mailing Service, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 4/23/68. #68-352, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Decision - Fights & Altercations, Insubordination
- Grand Ford Inc. vs. Local 259, UAW, 4/25/68. #68-358, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- American Stevedoring Co. vs. Local 701, IBT, 5/3/68. #68-359, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Negligence & Carelessness
- Simon's Warehouse Company, Inc. vs. Local 138, IBT, 4/15/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 1)
- Hyde Park Restaurant vs. Local 15, Bartenders Union, 4/30/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 2)
- Industrial Acoustics Company vs. Local 400, Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 5/4/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 3)
  Decision - Discharge, Tardiness, Absences
- Progress Electric Light Inc. vs. Local 710, Upholsterers International Union (UIU), 5/4/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 4)
  Decision - Overtime, Rates of Pay, Holiday Pay
- Alberts Beauty Salon vs. Local 1551A, Beauty Culturists Union (BCU), 5/6/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 5)
  Decision - Contract Interpretation, Financial Irresponsibility
- Taurone Label Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 5/6/69, 1969 (Box 7.1, Folder 6)
- Almissy Realty Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 5/13/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 7)
- J & M Furniture Company, Inc. vs. Local 853, Retail Furniture and Floor Covering Union, 5/13/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 8)
  Decision - Lay- off
- Borinquen Sweing, Inc. vs. Local 118, Fur, Leather, Plastic and Novelty Workers Union, 5/18/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 9)
- Aywon Wire and Metal Co. vs. Local 719, International Production, Service and Sale Employees Union, 6/4/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 10)
- Consolidated Loose-Leaf Inc. vs. Local 210, IBT, 6/5/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 11)
- Arfre Luncheonette Inc. vs. Local 1199, RDWSU, 6/11/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 12)
- Krug Baking Company vs. Local 50, ABCWU, 6/12/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 13)
- Park Reservoir Housing Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 6/12/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 14)
- Taurone Label Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 6/15/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 15)
- A Janis vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 6/22/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 16)
- Churchill's Restaurant, Inc. vs. Local 1, Dining Room Employees Union, 6/22/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 17)
- Gordon Baking Company vs. Local 450, ABCWU, 6/25/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 18)
- R.C. Allen Business Machines Company vs. Local 459, IUE, 6/26/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 19)
- Joseph Swick vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 7/1/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 20)
  Decision - Contract Negotiation
- Radio Wire and TV Corporation vs. Local 431, IUE, 7/2/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 21)
- Continental Baking Company vs. Local 50, ABCWU, 7/2/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 22)
- Isaac Greenberg vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 7/6/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 23)
- A& B Typewriter vs. Local 477, IUE, 7/8/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 24)
- Eastern Bias Manufacturing Co. vs. New York Joint Board, TWUA, 7/8/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 25)
- Real Curtain Company vs. Greater New York Joint Board, TWUA, 9/10/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 26)
- J. Michaels Inc. vs. Local 635, Home Furnishing Employees Union, RCIA, 9/11/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 27)
- Grapal Realty Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 9/21/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 28)
- De San Hair Creations, Inc. vs. Local 1551, BCU, 9/29/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 29)
- Harry's Food Shop vs. Harlem Labor Union, 9/29/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 30)
- The Little Europa, Inc. vs. Local 1115, Restaurant, Dining Room Luncheonette Union, 9/30/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 31)
- Aaron Gelman and Julius Gordon vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 10/15/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 32)
- A. Moskowitz vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 10/19/59 (Box 7.1, Folder 33)
- Ames Handbag Inc. vs. Joint Board, International Leather Goods, Plastics, and Novelty Workers Union, 10/19/59 (Box 7.1, Folder 34)
- Security Products, Inc. vs. Local 517, International Production, Service and Sales Employees Union, 10/23/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 35)
- Julius Pollak and Sons, Inc. vs. Local 447, Printing Specialties and Paper products Union, 11/12/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 36)
- Tedoch Realty Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 11/13/59(?), 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 37)
- New York Rubber Corporation vs. Local 23453, Rubber Workers, 11/16/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 38)
- Dave's Clinway Luncheonette vs. Allied Trades Council, 11/23/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 39)
  Decision - Union Security, Financial Irresponsibility
- Aurora Electric Company, Inc. vs. Local 400, Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 11/25/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 40)
- Automobile Dealers Industrial Relations Association of New York, Inc. vs. Local 259, UAW, 11/25/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 41)
- George W. Anderson, Inc. vs. Local 447, Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union, 11/30/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 42)
- North American Aluminum Corporation vs. Local 258, Warehouse and Processing Workers Union, 12/10/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 43)
  Decision - Back Pay, Lay-off, Vacation
- Master Rule Manufacturing Co., Inc. vs. Local 2189, IAM, 12/11/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 44)
- Fifth Realty Corporation vs. Local 1, Independent Union of Building Service Employees, 12/14/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 45)
- National Gypsum Co. vs. District 50, UMW, 12/15/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 46)
- Bruart Realty Corp. vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 12/18/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 47)
- Pace Cut & Curl Physiognomical vs. Local 1551A, BCU, 12/18/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 48)
- Jack Sehres vs. Local 1034, Container, Drum and Miscellaneous Workers Union, 12/29/59, 1959 (Box 7.1, Folder 49)
- City of New York Department of Welfare vs. Local 371, AFSCME, 11/4/68. #68-360, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Findings of Fact and Recommendations, Fact Finder's Notes, Preliminary Drafts of Award, Advisory Recommendations, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Modification
- Sol Goldwasser vs. District 65, RWDSU, 7/11/68. #68-362, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Decision - Labor Arbitration Award
- S.Q.R., Inc. vs. Independent Workers of S.Q.R., Inc., 5/20/68. #68-365, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Decision - Absences
- Union Free School District #15 vs. Valhalla Teachers Association, 5/26/68. #68-366, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendations - Contract Modification (Wages & Fringe Benefits)
- Central School District #1, Somers vs. Somers Faculty Association, 12/12/68. #68-367., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Findings of Facts & Recommendations - Contract modification (Grievance Procedure)
- Northwest Airlines vs. Lodge 143, IAM, 10/1/68. #68-368, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Decision - Interpretation of Past Labor Arbitration Award
- Scientific Coating Co., Inc. vs. Local 834, PDPA, 6/25/58. #68-369, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Decision - Jurisdiction
- Simmons Co. vs. Simmons Elizabeth Employees Union, 8/27/68. #68-370, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Decision - Layoffs
- Overland Fabrics vs. District 65, RWDSU, 6/18/68 #68-371, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Decision - Moving of Business
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. Local 1212, IBEW, 7/68. #68-372, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Decision - Contracting Out
- Okonite Company vs. Local 1992, IBEW, 9/17/68. #68-373, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Decision - Layoff, Notice
- Weston Instruments, Inc. vs. Weston Employees Union 12/12/68. #68-374, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Decision - Lunch Periods, Past Practice
- Elastic Stop Nut Corporation of America vs. Local 726, UAW, 7/11/68. #68-375, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Decision - Reporting Pay, Sick Pay, Assignment to Work Outside Classification
- Kraft Food Co. vs. Local 56, AFAW, 3/5/69. #68-377, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Warren Automatic Controls Corp. vs. District 9, USWA, 7/17/68. #68-378, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Decision - Seniority Status, Sick Leave and Sick Pay, Overtime
- Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority vs. Local 234, TWU, 2/1/69. #68-379, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Decision - Intoxication
- New Era Letter Co. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 7/19/68. #68-380 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Williams Press, Inc. vs. No. 23, APPAOWU, 6/6/68. #68-381, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Decision - Testing of Employees
- R.H. Macy & Co. vs. Local 804, IBT, 7/25/68., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Metromedia, Inc. vs. Local 794, Television Broadcasting Studio Employees Union (TBSEU), 12/11/68. #68-383, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  Decision - Contracting Out, Work Justification
- David and Ella Horowitz vs. Local 377, United Service Employees, 1/14/60, 1960 (Box 8.1, Folder 1)
- Hen-Al Realty Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 1/14/60, 1960 (Box 8.1, Folder 2)